Subtitle edited by - Aorion -
"Friend Request (2016)" ^ (Run time 01:32:14)
Everyone, please.
Please.
It's my unfortunate
responsibility
to share with you
some terrible news.
It seems that over the weekend
a fellow student Marina mills
committed suicide.
'Is it true that she filmed it
on her webcam?'
One of your classmates died
and all you care about
is whether you can see it?
Apparently, there was
a video uploaded
to the university website
this morning.
Some of you were
crafty enough to grab it
before we could take it down.
I urge you not to,
to watch it.
'Anyone caught sharing it
will be suspended, period.'
'no discussion.'
Were any of you friends
with Marina?
'Or have any info that can
shed light on this tragedy?
'If so, see me after class.'
Liv, this video is so cute.
- So not scary.
- Yeah, right.
This is so good.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Someone didn't come home
last night.
Yeah, again.
So are you guys, like,
monogamous now or what?
Liv, it's not
a dirty word. Jesus.
I know. Clearly, I'm just
jealous, you know, being dumped.
You were not dumped.
You knew him for one day.
It was an amazing day.
Hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, like that? Yeah.
- Eww.
- Oh, my god.
- 'Hmm. I know.'
- This is crazy.
So you're in a,
in a relationship?
- Oh, here we go.
- No, it's super cool. Really.
I just, you know, love all
these precious little updates
about you and Dr. surfboard.
- Good for you.
- Oh, shut up.
Another argument
that Internet addiction disorder
doesn't belong in the dsm
'is that it's frequently
symptomatic of other disorders.'
'depression, anxiety, trauma.'
often, it's an escape from
things we don't wanna deal with.
From our everyday lives
to things far, far worse.
Though the most common disorder
might just be
that we have too much time
on our hands.
Play it cool.
Wait a few days.
He already knows I'm not cool.
I think we might have
an excellent example
of Internet addiction disorder
right here in class.
'Beside from miss woodson
and miss mathison'
'does anyone else here
experience symptoms?'
- look at that.
- I love it. I like that.
- That's a nice one.
- Oh, I really like that filter.
- I can show you how to do it.
- 'Look at Kobe. Jesus.'
'When's he gonna get over you?'
'He's such a creeper.'
- 'He is not a creeper!'
- Oh.
Who's that?
A girl in my class.
'Zero friends.
How's that not, like, super weird?'
'Maybe she just started
her profile or something.'
Is she like 12 years old?
Ha. I think
she's really talented.
I like it.
You like it when she rips
her hair out during class?
- Oh, come on.
- 'Ew.'
'I literally saw her
pull an eyelash out today.'
Uh, it's a condition.
It's called trichotillomania.
You would know all about it
if you crack open a textbook
every once in a while.
- Owned.
- 'Oh, whatever.'
I'm actually changing majors
next year.
Oh, yeah,
and the year after that?
- Owned! Twofer.
- Come on.
Whatever.
'Oh, what are you making?'
'Is that seafood curry?
Oh, it's good.'
'What? Seafood curry.
No, this is..'
'Well, my dad
was a psychiatrist'
so I guess I, you know,
wanna follow in his footsteps.
That's nice.
Are you doing it for credit
or you just..
You really wanna do it?
I'm not sure.
I just transferred.
- I-I don't know anyone yet.
- Well, now you know me.
Are you in the dorms?
My friends and I,
we just got an apartment.
It's amazing,
but we're definitely
not getting any work done.
- Too many friends.
- Exactly.
I'll see you around campus.
Bye, Laura.
I thought med students
had homework.
- You wanted to talk.
- Well, I'm studying.
Internet addiction disorder.
And you're your own case study.
Exactly.
What's the deal with this girl?
I don't know.
I think she's lonely.
Is she gonna be your friend
or your first mental patient?
She'll be my second
mental patient.
'She's going through every post
I've ever made in my life.'
Wow.
She's crazy.
Look, look what
she just sent me.
What, I wanna see.
Oh.
Uh.
Oh, you guys are gonna live
happily ever after together.
- Oh, my god.
- How nice.
- Who is this person?
- I don't know.
Dude, scroll down.
I wanna see her timeline.
'Further.'
Whoa.
'Jesus.'
'No wonder this girl's
giving you nightmares.'
close it.
- Oh.
- Oh, my god.
Laura, this girl isn't right.
Why are you hanging out
with her?
I was just trying to be nice.
God! I can't believe you invited
her to your birthday.
No, no, no, no.
I didn't invite her.
She invited herself.
What was I supposed to say?
Um, how about something
like, fuck, no?
Yeah, that sounds
about right to me.
You can't say that to someone.
- Oh, yeah. It goes like this.
- Yes, you can.
It goes like this. "Hey, Laura,
can I come to your birthday?"
- Fuck, no!
- There you go.
Laura, finally.
Happy birthday.
- You look so pretty.
- Thanks, Marina.
- 'You get my messages?'
- Yeah, how can I miss them?
Are you mad at me?
Did I do something wrong?
No, I'm not mad at you,
I'm just..
I'll see you
in class tomorrow, okay?
But what about tonight?
Aren't you celebrating
with your friends?
Uh, it's just
Tyler and I tonight.
We're going out to dinner, so..
Just the two of us.
'But you barely know her.'
Isn't tonight just you
and your friends?
I know,
I know.
I just feel, you know,
icky lying about it.
Well, you don't look
very icky to me.
Go ahead.
Hi.
Hi, Mom.
- Hey, happy birthday.
- Hi.
I've been trying to get
your Mom as drunk as possible.
'You actually knew a beautiful guy'
You need to get drunk with me,
so we know..
Yeah, it's literally hurt 'em
so they started to praise it.
'And the last reason,
no matter what'
that you'll always find
some crazy way
to make me feel better.
'Aww.'
'Wait, wait, wait,
to my little green bean'
who makes me so proud every day
and who made her father
so proud every single second.
Oh, Mom.
'Alright, I'm getting in.'
I'm bumping
in this little love boat.
No, I'm going, I'm going, okay?
Uh, this is, this is to us.
A-a wonderful evening.
'To, to the future,
to success.'
and you shut up,
you drunk floozy.
And then this is also
to, to just to you.
A happy birthday.
Thanks you, guys.
- Hey, Laura. How are you doing?
- Hey, how are you?
- I'm good.
- That's good.
I thought we were friends.
Marina, what are,
what are you talking about?
I saw you with everyone.
Your birthday dinner.
- I saw it.
- Marina, I'm sorry.
I, I didn't mean
to hurt your feelings.
Can we talk about this
later, okay?
I had a present for you.
I worked on it for two weeks.
Two weeks? You've barely
known me for two weeks.
You fucking liar,
you're just like everyone else!
Why did you accept
my friend request?
- You didn't have to do that!
- Get the fuck off me!
Do you have any idea
what it feels to be alone?
- Completely alone..
- Get off me, you freak!
Laura, you didn't do
anything wrong.
This chick is just damaged.
You weren't there, Tyler.
It's not your fault.
Baby, I'm really sorry.
'I gotta get back
to cutting up dead people.'
okay.
She's tryin' to face-chat me.
What do I do?
Don't take the call.
Seriously.
Fine, alright.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
Bye.
Liv?
Hmm.
Are you okay?
'Go to bed.'
Let me after class
to tell you a story..
'Please.
Everyone, please.'
It's my unfortunate
responsibility
to share with you
some terrible news.
It seems that over the weekend
your fellow student
Marina mills committed suicide.
How'd it go?
Fine.
I just told them
she was stalking me.
Kind of like crazy.
Hey, don't beat
yourself up about it.
That girl was completely nuts.
She needed help though.
Yeah, like serious help.
Never miss sophomore
in psych 201.
'Look on the bright side.'
might be able to get
out of class for the funeral.
No-no-no, there's not gonna be
a funeral. There's no body.
What do you mean?
Uh, um, cops were at my dorm
this morning
and, and they don't know where
she did it, but it wasn't there.
'Uh, actually, she hasn't swiped
her keycard since last weekend.'
and that's not what freaks
me out, what freaks me out
is that they don't know
who this girl even was.
Her, uh, contact info,
her social security,
it's all been deleted
from the school database.
'They don't even think that
Marina mills was her real name.'
Uh, are you serious?
- Oh, my god.
- What's going on?
Why are you watching this?
- Who sent you this crap?
- 'She did.'
- she's dead.
- I know.
Again, you'll have 60 minutes.
This is an actual case study.
A challenging one.
Oh, my god.
God.
Is that the video?
I thought you said it was
in your messages. You posted it?
No, no, someone did.
I didn't.
And they tagged all my friends.
Laptops away, Miss Woodson.
Why would they think I did that?
I would, I would never do that.
Did you try
changing your password?
Yes, yes, I've tried everything.
She's even back
in my friend's list.
Unfriend that dead bitch.
I can't.
So according to you,
miss woodson, this video
just magically appeared
on your timeline this morning?
- Do I have that right?
- Why would I do this?
There must be some reason this
girl burned that picture of you.
Look, Laura, we know
that you're a great student
but multiple students
reported you harassing Marina.
No, she was the one
harassing me.
She was obsessed with me.
Laura, no one's saying
it's your fault
that Marina took her life.
We're looking into everything.
But in the meantime, Laura,
if you can't delete that video
'you're gonna have
to delete your profile.'
Hey, one more thing.
Any idea where this girl
might have torched herself?
No.
No, you're not listening to me.
I can't delete this video.
I can't even delete my account.
'Like I said,
this isn't a call center.'
Okay, well, what about that
dead girl I can't unfriend?
Can you do somethingabout that?
'Ma'am, I'm not seeing
this profile.'
What?
I just saw it!
Is there anyone else
I can speak to?
'I'm afraid they'll just
tell you the same thing.'
What's next?
Kobe, I know you're in there.
I can hear your stupid game.
That was a nice video
you posted.
Yeah, that's what
I'm here about.
Wow.
You're her only friend.
How special is that?
Shut up.
Christ, someone's still uploading things.
That, that's intense.
I fuckin' love it.
Oh, alright.
Okay, let's take a little peek
behind the curtains.
'What?'
You have no idea
how crazy that is, do you?
Okay.
Look at that.
'Look, that, that is what code
normally looks like.'
Not this.
I-I can't even copy this.
This isn't, this isn't code.
Well, w-what is it?
I don't know.
Wait, wait.
Can you go back?
'Just stop looking
at that girl's profile.'
'Stop thinking about her.'
She killed herself.
End of story.
She burned and hung herself
in front of her laptop.
'Who does that?'
Is this gonna be a thing now?
You and Kobe hangin' out
in his dorm room.
Is that really what you're
thinking about right now?
Yeah, I'm thinking about us.
What's wrong with that?
He's just a friend,
you know that.
Does he?
'It's called cyberstalking
for a reason.'
They can't bother you
if you're not online.
'Uh, yeah.
Get me some of those'
'Uh, chocolate macadamia
crisp thingies.'
'No, they're not, uh, like,
chocolate potato chips.'
'They're like cookies.'
'Like, uh, crackers, kind of.'
Just ask the guy there.
I go there all the time.
The white chubby kid
who loves chocolate.
Babe, you're not chubby.
You're very fussy. My god!
I'm not being fussy,
I'm on my period
and chocolate makes me
feel better.
Isabel?
Hello?
Shit.
Chad?
Hello?
Kobe?
You guys, this isn't funny.
Seriously.
Guys?
Kobes, come on, man.
What the hell?
What...
What the fuck.
'No, no, no, no, no.'
Oh.
No!
'No!'
Okay, so she's barely
talking right now.
They're gonna her overnight.
Maybe longer.
You can see her if you want.
Listen, I didn't know
Gustavo that well.
Was he on something?
No.
I saw the medical report.
It is insane.
Please, just leave.
'Sweetheart.'
This is all her fault.
She's not herself, Laura.
No, Gus wasn't himself.
'He was having nightmares.'
so am I.
You're scaring us, is.
What are you talking about?
Laura knows!
She knows.
It doesn't feel real.
Promise me you won't look
at that girl's profile today.
You're drivin' yourself crazy.
Delete your account.
Seriously.
You want Isabel to see that?
Liv, you know I can't.
I don't care how.
Just do it.
Fuck.
Even if it's not you
behind these posts
I'm getting a lot of pressure
from the students.
As long as the posts are up,
I have no choice
but to suspend you
for the rest of the semester.
Mom, you don't always have to
call me on facetime, you know.
- Why didn't you call me?
- I'm sorry.
I, I didn't want you
to worry, okay?
I'm coming to pick you up.
I want you home.
No. Look, look, I'll call you later.
I promise, okay?
Look at that.
What the hell.
Yeah, she friended him
right before he died.
There's something else.
- Jesus, Kobe, I don't...
- I don't want you to watch it.
I want you to listen.
What is that?
I don't know. I think it's wasps.
She's got black wasps
all over her profile.
'I did some research, and, um'
'some people associated them
with evil.'
They say they appeared
wherever witches lived.
They, like, follow them
around and protect them.
Jesus.
Who is this girl?
Do you think you could
get us into her room?
Come on, now.
Not much into fashion, was she?
Do you even know
what you're looking for?
Well, just anything.
Oh, hey, hey.
Look, look, look.
- 'That's her.'
- 'And who are these two?'
Can you find
what school this is?
If it's ever been online, yeah.
Are you the young lady
who called?
Marina's friend?
Yes.
How close did you say
you were again?
I was just getting
to know her when she..
I didn't even know
her real name.
Nedifar, Marina nedifar.
Do you know what happened
to her parents?
I wouldn't know
anything about that.
She came to us
as a ward of the state.
Poor girl, she had such
a rough go of things here.
She was always very sensitive.
Always alone.
Fleeing into her little fantasy worlds.
And she found some
dark corners online.
Things no child should see.
Sometimes she would just stare
at the computer for hours.
Nothing on the screen at all.
Just her own reflection
in the darkness.
The kids became terrified of her.
They said she gave them nightmares.
Fuck!
Jesus.
The two boys in the photo
they were found dead
near saddle mills
with their faces mutilated.
They were swarmed
by black wasps.
What?
Tyler, I know you could get
in trouble for this
but please, can you...
can you access
her records somehow?
Like a family contact
or the last address?
'Something?'
We don't even know
her last name.
Nedifar.
Marina nedifar.
Laura?
Hello?
Is anybody here?
This is not real.
No.
This is not real!
'Miss Woodson.'
She rips out her own hair
before she slits her throat.
'Now I've been
on this job 25 years'
and that's a first for me.
There's some shitty new drug
we don't know about?
I never took anything.
What I wanna know is, where
you got the elevator footage
that you posted.
For the last time,
I'm not posting any of this.
Well, the good news for you
is we can't link
your ip address
to any of these videos.
'We couldn't find
any address at all'
which doesn't make any sense.
Unless you are familiar
with our it department.
It all has to do with this girl.
You really know a lot
of dead people, miss woodson.
This is not real!
I don't think
this was a suicide, Laura.
I think it was a ritual.
Um, that,
what you're lookin' at here
these are,
these are black mirrors.
'They've been used in the occult
for thousands of years.'
'And they say that if you,
if you stare into it'
you can communicate
with some other sides.
'It's, it's,
it's called scrying.'
But sometimes these witches,
if they were being hunted
if they didn't have any other,
any other way out,
'they would hang
and burn themselves'
in front of a black mirror
and become something else.
Call it whatever you want.
An evil spirit.
Um, a, a demon.
'Point is, it's how
they got revenge on people.'
Uh, possessing them
and-and haunting them
and killing them.
How'd they ever stop it?
It says they had to find
the original mirror.
The one they burned themselves
in front of, destroy it.
You mean her laptop?
It was her black mirror.
'We need to find out
where she killed herself.'
Oh.
Oh, my god.
I mean, there, there has
to be something here.
You know, something
that can help us.
I think I'm going home.
I can't handle this.
I'm so sorry for everything.
- Please, don't go.
- I'm sorry.
I can't.
You're late.
Why is everyone
talking about you?
What have you done to this girl?
I haven't done anything to her.
She just attached herself to me.
And now everyone thinks that..
Please, I want you home, baby.
You're coming home with me.
Well, I can't. I can't. I have
to stay and figure it out.
Figure what out?
...suffered serious injuries.
Police have the suspect in custody
but they're not releasing
any information
until they complete their investigation.
'Moore's grove.'
It's a deserted farm town
about two hours away.
There was a fire there
20 years ago
at some weird commune.
Marina's mother, Ada nedifar,
lived there
'until somebody burnt
the whole place down.'
What?
They kept some husk
of her body alive...
until Marina was delivered.
She was alone
in the womb for months.
Jesus, she was always alone.
You think this is where
she went to kill herself?
I mean, it's the only lead
we have.
What going on with her profile?
What's that on there?
'Hey, it's Olivia.
Leave me a ping.'
Something's wrong,
something's wrong.
Stop right here.
Stop right here and let me out.
Oh, my god.
'Oh, my god.'
'Olivia.'
Get out, get out and help her.
- Help her.
- Save me.
- 'Thank you so much, doctor.'
- 'Yeah.'
She's stable.
She might actually
make it through this.
Even if she does...
Marina's never gonna stop.
Shit.
Just, just stay here.
Stay with Liv, please.
Don't let her be alone.
Wh-where are you going?
Whoa!
Someone had a rough day.
What happens if there's still
people living here? I mean..
What is this place now?
I don't know.
No matter what,
I'm finding that laptop
and I'm gonna fuckin' smash it.
- Kobe.
- Yeah.
Thanks for coming with me.
Who says I'm doing it for you?
'Where the hell are you?'
The cops are asking me
a million questions.
I'm-I'm going to Moore's grove.
I'm sorry.
Don't go there alone.
I, I'm not alone.
I'm, I'm with Kobe.
I'm coming to meet you.
So, where is she?
I don't know, man.
Bad reception.
- Yeah.
- Alright, keep trying.
Shit.
- Charming.
- 'Yeah.'
Thanks.
Shit, there's no service.
What are you so fuckin' nervous about?
You're gonna be fine.
What are you talking about?
You said she wants
to make you lonely.
If that's true, then you are
the only one that's safe.
Oh, hey, sweetheart.
I said no.
No Chinese for you.
N-no, no, no,
I-I said no Chinese.
No Chinese, I said..
Sure, yeah, no, I mean, we-we
could have Chinese, alright.
From down...
No, down at the one by the..
Yeah, I'll call you back.
Please, no. I don't wanna die.
Please, please.
'Oh, my god.'
Really?
Laura.
- Kobe.
- What?
She's not here.
Did you check the basement?
What basement?
'Kobe.'
Kobe.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
She can't make you lonely
if you're dead.
Laura!
Laura.
'Hey, it's Laura.
Leave a message.'
What do you mean
you don't know where she is?
What happened back there?
Hey, don't you know
I'm fucking talking to you?
What happened?
Listen to me, if you touch her,
I'll fuckin' kill you.
- Now where the hell is she?
- She is absolutely fine.
We are completely fucked.
She's just peachy.
Tyler.
Laura, thank god. I thought
something happened to you.
I-I just texted you an address.
Laura, I-I cant,
I can't hear you.
You're breaking up.
Tyler.
'Are you sure you don't want me
to take you to a hospital?'
Take me to the factory.
So you think we can beat this,
don't you?
Shut up, man.
Seriously.
You have no idea
what we're dealing with.
I do.
I saw where we're headed...
- Shut up, man, seriously...
- I fucking saw it.
'You're telling me
you're gonna die for her.'
Because we've all
been dying for her!
You can stay in the car, man.
Mom.
Laura, where have you been?
I can't reach you.
- Mom, are you okay?
- I'm seeing things, Laura.
- I keep seeing that girl.
- I'm sorry.
- It's my fault.
- What's happening to us?
Listen to me. I'm not gonna
let anything happen to you.
I'm gonna sort this out somehow.
I'm gonna stop this somehow.
'Mom?'
- Mom! Mom!
- 'I'm gonna protect you.'
Mom!
Mom.
'Laura.'
'Laura!'
Tyler.
I was so worried about you.
Laura, hey.
Laura, look at me.
My Mom, she's...
Jesus.
What happened to you?
Hi.
What do you want from me?
What else do you want from me?
'I just wanna be friends, Laura.'
Best friends.
Forever.
'Laura.'
'Come to me.'
Subtitle edited by - Aorion -